Class of 1904 Records, 1900-1979
Smith College Archives
Class of 1904 Records
1900-1979
Smith College. Class of 1904.
RG 80 UUID:a34d8da5-3553-47fc-8c53-71f7427c2752
10 boxes (4.2 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 10 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1904.
The Class of 1904 was the twenty-sixth entering class and the twenty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1904 records, 1900-1979, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1904, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, photo albums, letters, class secretary's notebook, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1904 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 1)
- Bequests 1968-1971 (Box 1645, Folder 2)
- Clippings 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 3)
- Commencement 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 5)
- Commencement Photographs 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 6)
- Commencement Speaker 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 7)
- Freshman Frolic given by 1903 1900 (Box 1645, Folder 8)
- Freshman Grind by 1903 1900 (Box 1645, Folder 9)
- Freshman Handbook 1900 (Box 1645, Folder 10)
- Groups 1900-1904 (Box 1645, Folder 11)
- Groups- Photographs 1900-1904 (Box 1645, Folder 12)
- Class History undated (Box 1645, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 14)
- Ivy Day- Photographs 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 15)
- Junior Prom 1903 (Box 1645, Folder 16)
- Junior-Senior Party 1904 (Box 1645, Folder 17)
- Junior Ushers 1903 (Box 1645, Folder 18)
- Junior Frolic 1903 (Box 1645, Folder 19)
- Smith Alumnae Quarterly, Class Notes 1944-1977 (Box 1645, Folder 20)
- Class Letters 1944-1977 (Box 1645, Folder 21)
- Senior Dramatics 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics- Photographs 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 3)
- Scholarships 1964-1974 (Box 1646, Folder 4)
- Songs undated (Box 1646, Folder 5)
- Sophomore Reception 1901 (Box 1646, Folder 6)
- Class Supper 1904 (Box 1646, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Notebook 1907-1957 (Box 1647, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Notebook 1954-1977 (Box 1647, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Notebook 1905-1954 (Box 1647, Folder 3)
- Photograph Album (Box 1648, Folder 1)
- Photograph Album (Box 1648, Folder 2)
- Photograph Album (Box 1648, Folder 3)
- Reunions (Box 1649, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1905 (Box 1649, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1907 (Box 1649, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1909 (Box 1649, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1910 (Box 1649, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1919 (Box 1649, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1924 (Box 1649, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1925 (Box 1649, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1929 (Box 1649, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1934 (Box 1649, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1939 (Box 1649, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 1649, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1950-1952 (Box 1649, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 1649, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1958 (Box 1649, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 1649, Folder 16)
- Reunions- Photographs 1964 (Box 1649, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 1649, Folder 18)
- Reunion Album 1959 (Box 1650, Folder 1)
- Reunion Album 1959 (Box 1650, Folder 2)
- Reunion Album 1959 (Box 1650, Folder 3)
- Reunion Scrapbook- missing since 2/99 (Box 1651, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 1952, Folder 1)
- Reunions- Photographs 1969 (Box 1952, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 1952, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 1952, Folder 4)
- Reunion Scrapbook- missing since 2/99 (Box OV)
- Reunion Bags (Box OV)